Hi! In this video, I'm going to explain very quickly how to work
こんにちは！ このビデオでは、Railsmaniaのオンライン開発環境
with our online development environment. The development environment has
の操作方法を説明します。この開発環境は,
just the right amount of functionality needed to help you develop your applications
アプリケーション開発を支援するために必要な最低限の
without being overly complicated.
機能だけが含まれています
On the left we have the files view. Every account comes with a workspace directory.
左にファイルビューがあります。すべてのアカウントには、ワークスペースディレクトリが付属しています。
We can click on that directory to expand it. To open a file, simply
そのディレクトリを展開すると内容が見えます。ファイルを
click on it once.
開くために、ファイル名を一度クリックしてください。
If you right click on a directory, you can see an option to add files or to add directories.
ディレクトリを右クリックすると、ファイルを追加するか、ディレクトリを追加するためのオプションが表示されます。
Choosing either of these options will allow you to select files from your local machine to upload.
これらのオプションのいずれかを選択すると、ファイルの選択画面が表示されます。
You can select one or more files and click ok, and it will upload them
つまたは複数のファイルを選択して、[OK]をクリックすると、
to your workspace.
あなたのワークスペースにアップロードします。
In our development environment, you'll have plenty of space to host all the files you need for a
開発環境では、一般的なアプリケーションに必要なすべてのファイルをホストでき
typical Rails application.
十分なスペースがあります。
The main part of the window, on the right side, is used by the editor view.
右側に、エディタビューがあります。
It's an easy to use, simple code editor with syntax highlighting for Ruby.
これは、Rubyのコマンドをハイライトできるシンプルなコードエディタです。
When we modify any file, you will see this mark.
ファイルを変更するとこのマークが表示されます。
Indicating that the file is not yet saved.
そのファイルがまだ保存されていないという意味です。
To save the file, select [ Editor - Save ] from the menu bar.
ファイルを保存するために、メニューバーから[Edit -> Save]を選択するか
Or use the standard shortcut keys to save, such as Ctrl+S on Windows or
Macでコマンド+S、Windowsでコントロール+Sを使用
Cmd+S on Mac.
してください
The file will be saved in our cloud environment and will be accessible from any of your devices.
ファイルは、クラウド環境に保存され、あなたのデバイスのいずれからもアクセスできるようになります。
The last important component is the terminal view.
最後の重要な構成要素は、ターミナルです。
Our development environment gives you access to a Linux Debian environment
開発環境を使用すると、完全な権限を持つLinuxのDebianシステムにアクセスできます。
with full privileges. You have access to all the commands you may need.
あなたが必要なすべてのコマンドを使用できます。
In the lesson we will often use the "Rails" commands in the terminal, for instance:
レッスンで私たちはしばしば、ターミナルでRailsのコマンドを使用します。たとえ
we can execute Rails new such as "rails new new_project"
このようにrails newを実行します：　rails new new_project
and you can see how the files view automatically updated its contents
実行後にファイルビューが自動的にアップデートされて
with the new project that Rails created.
今作成した新しいプロジェクトの内容が表示されています。
Now we can move to this new directory using standard *Nix
次に、cd new_project のような*nixのコマンドを使用して、
commands like "cd new_project" and list the
この新しいディレクトリに移動し, lsのコマンドで
files with "ls"
ファイルを一覧表示することができます。
So that's it for this video, we hope you find this development environment both simple and useful.
このビデオはこれで終わりです。私たちは、あなたがこの開発環境がシンプルで便利だと実感できることを願っています。